stylemid.com 2012-06-10

# PRIVACY TERMS - Luxury shop online in STYLEMID.COM ITALY

Privacy Terms

Read the terms of privacy before sign up in STYLEMID.COM

Thank you for visiting our web site STYLEMID.COM 

Personal information sent via the Internet without using security procedures can be controlled by third parties. Because of the network structure of the Internet, data sent via the Internet may travel across international borders even though both sender and recipient are in the same country. This makes it possible that the data is transmitted in a country where standards of privacy protection are lower than the country of residence. MID26 srl assumes no responsibility for the security of data during transmission over the Internet.   
MID26 srl does not collect personal information on this site by way of business communication and promotion, MID26 srl may send either via Internet or through the mail, communications that are informative, cultural or business solely and exclusively by the people who make explicit request through specific forms. In this case, personal data will be processed and stored in accordance with applicable local law. MID26 srl reserves the right to use cookies to obtain non-personal information about the use of this Site, including IP address and the number of sessions.   
These data are collected solely to monitor usage and performance of the Site, Cookies are used to facilitate accessibility in the Site 

MID26 srl takes all necessary steps to prevent third parties or persons who, on his appointment process services, access to personal data. Under the law, MID26 srl will reveal personal information to third parties in compliance with legal provisions or regulations. In the event that data is stored outside of your country of residence MID26 srl will ensure adequate levels of data protection, taking into account the legal constraints and regulations, including those related to banking secrecy and data protection. 

The information, products and services provided on this website are not intended for distribution to, or use by persons or entities in any jurisdiction or country where such distribution or use are permitted by local laws or regulations or would subject Inpeco required to seek registration in those jurisdictions or countries. Any person or entity against whom such prohibitions apply must not access the site or use it. 

This website, www.stylemid.com (hereinafter called "the Site") is owned by MID26 srl. Anyone accessing this site agrees to the terms contained herein, otherwise they must leave the site and do not use. 

MID26 srl controls any information on this site is accurate and current at the time of publication. However MID26 srl makes no representation that the information contained is ultimately reliable and complete. The information on this site are published with no warranty, express or implied. MID26 srl does not warrant that the information can be distorted due to technical malfunctions. Nothing contained in this website constitutes investment advice legal, tax or other advice nor should it be relied on in making investment or other decisions. Specific expertise and training is always required for any decision relating to investments. 

Under no circumstances, including negligence, MID26 srl be liable for damages of any kind. The site may contain links (links) to other sites. The links are provided only as references to information on topics that may be useful to users. Through the links that may be present in this site, you can leave the site MID26 srl does not control the sites linked to its website and accepts no responsibility for the content of such websites nor the products or services and other services offered by them. MID26 srl does not warrant that such sites or their content are free from claims relating to copyright, trademarks or other violations of rights of third parties or that such websites or their content are free of viruses or other contamination. There is no guarantee as to the authenticity of documents on the Internet. Links to websites outside of MID26 srl. does not imply approval or responsibility for the opinions, ideas, products, information or services in such sites, or any representation regarding the content of such sites. Acting on an outside link, you are interacting with a third-party site that may exploit any vulnerabilities in the browser to gain control of the session MID26 srl. directly from the user's computer. MID26 srl. does not warrant or represent that the linked website or any software present in it meet the requirements in effect as regards the content, conduct, reliability, no interruption, timeliness, security, or errors.
